Contact

rnsrsuper@outlook.com

www.linkedin.com/in/jennifer-bass-2a5028121 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Healthcare

Customer Service

Hospitals

Certifications

ACLS

TNCC

BLS

Honors-Awards

Daisy Award

Jennifer Bass

BSN RN

Houston, Texas

Summary

Experienced Travel Nurse with a demonstrated history of working in the staffing and recruiting industry. Skilled in Microsoft Word, Critical Care Nursing, Healthcare Management, Healthcare, and Leadership. Strong healthcare services professional with a Bachelor's degree focused in Nursing Science from The University of Texas at Arlington.

Experience

HCA Healthcare

5 years

RN SICU

December 2017 - Present (2 years 7 months)

Houston, Texas

RN IMCU

July 2015 - December 2017 (2 years 6 months)

HealthTrust Workforce Solutions
Travel Registered Nurse

August 2017 - Present (2 years 11 months)

Tenet Health Systems
Registered Nurse
July 2015 - August 2017 (2 years 2 months)

Education

The University of Texas at Arlington
Bachelor's degree, Nursing Science · (2015 - 2017)

Lone Star College

Associate of Science - AS, Registered Nursing/Registered Nurse \cdot (2013 - 2015)

Walden University AG-ANCP · (2019)